## **Python Developer**

# JAROSŁAW WYGODA

igwedge

jaroslaw@wygoda.me

U

48517663382

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jarosławwygoda-869039155

jwygoda

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### Homeppl | since May 2020

As a consultant I've helped Homeppl team migrate django application to microservices architecture.

#### PatientSource | October 2019 - April 2020

As a consultant I've helped PatientSource team introduce devops-centered development process and support them with day-to-day development process.

#### Netguru | October 2018 - September 2019

Developing platform managing and optimising online advertising campaigns. Collaborating with London based advertising agency. Supporting R&D initiatives, estimating projects, presales activities, participating in scoping sessions and expert calls, code reviews. Technologies: Python, Django, Postgres, Docker, Terraform, CloudFormation, Zappa (serverless), AWS services, BigQuery, Git

#### WhiteAster | January 2018 - October 2018

Integrating machine learning solutions. Collaborating with New York based fintech company providing daily cashflow to Amazon suppliers. Technologies: Python, Django, Flask, TensorFlow, Pandas, NumPy, SciPy, JavaScript, Vue.js, AWS services, Git

#### Freelancing | October 2016 - January 2018

Developing e-commerce platforms, content management systems, web scraping scripts and payment gateways. Some projects I worked on: Project management system and lead generation scripts for advertisement company Q-Graf. Payment system for Tylicz ski resort. Technologies: Python, Django, Wagtail, django-payments, Saleor, Docker, Javascript, Git

### **EDUCATION**

## I was going to be a musician before I fell in love with programming.

Music School - Cello | 2008 - 2016

## **SKILLS**

My main domain of expertise are Django web applications.

## **About** me

Hi, my name is Jarosław Wygoda. I'm more than a programmer, I'm a problem solver. My day-to-day work involves understanding business needs and expressing it in software. I'm a back end engineer with strong devops skills and experience in developing user interfaces.